<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Show Me Your Hands</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ShowMeYourHands</packageId>
  <author>Mlie, Killface</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ShowMeYourHands</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>MalteSchulze.RIMMSqol</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <incompatibleWith>
    <li>Mlie.ClutterWeaponHands</li>
  </incompatibleWith>
  <description>

Pawns show their hands on their weapon when drafted. 
Should work with most weapons, vanilla and modded.

Based on &lt;b&gt;Clutter Weapon Hands&lt;/b&gt; but dynamically sets the hands based on the graphics of the weapon. It will however still use the old hand-definitions if they exist.

There is also mod-settings where you can modify the settings for each weapon. These settings can be exported and included in a mod to add native support.
All my "Continued"-mods should have native support.

There is also support for &lt;b&gt;Enable Oversized Weapons, Yayo's Combat 3, Yayo's Combat 3 Adopted, Yayo's Animation, RunAndGun&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Dual Wield.&lt;/b&gt; Hands will follow the weapons even during the extra animations. 
Verified to work with &lt;b&gt;Combat Extended&lt;/b&gt;
Also shows hands when using &lt;b&gt;Grab your Tool&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;size=24&gt;Settings&lt;/size&gt;
· Coloring the hands based on apparel/armor color
· Coloring the hands based on artificial limbs
· Resizing the hands based on the bodysize of the pawn, this also works with &lt;b&gt;Children&lt;/b&gt;
· Repositioning the hands based on the weaponsize, to support oversized weapons
· Showing the hands when pawns carry stuff
· Showing only one hand if the pawn is missing one
· Showing the hands at all times

&lt;size=24&gt;Credits&lt;/size&gt;
&lt;color=orange&gt;Arcanant&lt;/color&gt; for providing hand-definitions for a lot of mods.
&lt;color=orange&gt;Telefonmast&lt;/color&gt; for the support with the texture-code.
&lt;color=orange&gt;qux&lt;/color&gt; for the updated hand-texture.
&lt;color=orange&gt;shiuanyue&lt;/color&gt; for the Chinese translation.
Preview-image includes armor and weapons from the excellent XCOM-mods by &lt;color=orange&gt;velcroboy333&lt;/color&gt; - XCOM Armor · XCOM Weapons


Since modding is just a hobby for me I expect no donations to keep modding. If you still want to show your support you can gift me anything from my store.steampowered.com/wishlist/id/Mlie &lt;b&gt;Wishlist&lt;/b&gt;or buy me a cup of tea.


&lt;size=24&gt;Troubleshooting&lt;/size&gt;
· See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
· If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
· Post your error-log using &lt;b&gt;HugsLib&lt;/b&gt; and command Ctrl+F12
· For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
· Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
· If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
</description>
</ModMetaData>